sporteklive.com 2019-08-03

# Privacy Policy - Sportek Live

This Privacy Policy governs the exact manner in which our site  **SportekLive.com  **uses, collects, maintains and discloses the information gathered from the readers (each, a “User”) of the http://www.sporteklive.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the entire website and all products and services offered by the SportekLive.com.

 **What information do we gather from our readers?**

We may collect personal identification information from readers in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.

Readers may be specifically asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our website anonymously. We will solely collect/gather personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

 **What do we use such information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * In order to personalize your experience

(Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

  * In order to improve our core website

(We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

  * In order to improve customer service

(Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

  * In order to administer a contest, promotion, giveaway or other site features
  * In order to send periodic emails

(The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.)

 **Do we use cookies in this website?**

Yes!! (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still access all the services by contacting us via  **Contact US page.**

 **How do we ensure protection of your information?**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information and data stored on our website.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside 3** **rd** **  parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or rent our beloved readers personal identification information to others. We may occasionally share several generic aggregated demographic information which are not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

We may also use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. All of these third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

 **Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by simply giving a visit to the dedicated Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

 **Google Analytics**

This blog uses the Google Analytics Advertising Features which may help us and a few third party vendors to use various important first party cookies such as the Google Analytics cookie or few other first-party identifiers, and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together.

As a visitor you have all the rights to opt out from the Google Analytics Advertising Features which has been in use on this blog through various Ads Settings or Ad Settings for mobile apps, or any other available means whatsoever.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. W, therefore, will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

SportekLive.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time whatsoever. But whenever we do that, we will surely revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You are acknowledging and also agreeing that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of all the latest modifications.

 **Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this website, you signify your full acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

 **Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: admin@sporteklive.com
